

# **Juan Pablo Llorente**

**Full Stack Web Developer** 

#### CONTACT

Buenos Aires, Argentina

juanpablollorentej@gmail.com

+54 11 3336-5620

in Juan-Pablo-Llorente

JuanPablo-Llorente

Portfolio

#### EDUCATION

#### **Henry Bootcamp**

Full Stack Web Developer

2021 - 2022

#### **Edutin Academy**

Some IT related courses 2021 - 2022

### **Raggio Technical School**

Master Builder 2015 - 2020

### LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native. English: Intermediate

#### INTERESTS













### **PROFILE**

I'm a 20 years old Full Stack Web Developer and Master Builder from Buenos Aires, Argentina. Mainly oriented to the Back End, though i like Front End too.

As a good lover of logic, performance and order, I always seek to perform in the user experience and write a clean code.

I'm passionate about the technological and computer world and I always find myself learning new things.

## **EXPERIENCE**

### **Full Stack Web Developer**

May 2022 - June 2022 Henry

An digital art e-commerce with a small social network system. Made with six more co-workers as final project.

### **Full Stack Web Developer**

April 2022 - May 2022 Henry

A SPA (Single Page Application) of a video games encyclopedia.

### **DevOps**

March 2022 - April 2022 **ABEM** 

Assembly of mining platforms and do their maintenance.

#### **AutoCAD Draftsman**

MT Arquitectura

Sept. 2020 - August 2021

Drawing of municipal plans.

# CERTIFICATES

Full Stack Web Developer - June 2022 →

Computer Security - May 2022 →

Mobile Phone Repair and Maintenance - May 2022 →

Fundamentals in Computer Science - May 2022 →

Introduction to C - July 2021 →

## MAIN SKILLS

- JavaScript
- Redux
- Express
- Sequelize

- HTML
- React
- Node
- PostgreSQL
- Git